Resume ID 55dd546a920d3

PERSONAL DETAIL

Name	Angga Ari Wijaya
Day of Birthday	1992-05-26
Nationality	Indonesia
Gender	MALE
Address	Jl. Ir. Ibrahim Zahier 2 Gg. 2E No. 34 Gresik - JATIM
Contact	+6285655479868
Email	anggadarkprince@gmail.com
Website	http://www.angga-ari.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a software developer who has been freelancing for 2 years, Basically I am a calm person and my strengths includes. I am very hard working and passionate about my work. Moreover I am at very ease when working in a team, and ready to be self learner. I always persistent and discipline. My weakness is public speaking, my communication skills which I am trying to improve day by day and I am a difficult type of person at socialize in new environment but I am working on it. It may be also positive sometimes. I love working with my passion about design and programming and been wanting to jump into it if there was an opportunity. That's all about me. My father's name is Mr. Mukiyar he is a pensioner my mother's name is Mrs. Muliana she is a house wife I have one elder bother his name Hadi Dwi Iswanto and one elder sister her name Linda Ika Yuliana. That's all about my family. Thank you.

EDUCATION

Specialised Coursework	2014 - 2015
Game-Dev Corner Class - Sketch Project	Jember, Indonesia
Bachelors Degree	2010 - 2015
University of Jember - Information System	Jember, Indonesia
Senior High School	2007 - 2010
SMK Semen Gresik - Otomotive Mechanic	Gresik, Indonesia

Junior High School	2004 - 2007
SMP Negeri 4 Gresik	Gresik, Indonesia
Elementary School	1998 - 2004

EXPERIENCE

Sketch Project Studio	2014 - Now	
Game & media interactive development	Founder & Game Programming	
Lab Assistance	2012 - 2014	
Teaching, developing, computer maintenance	Programming Assistance	
CV Dwi Raksa Gresik Training	2009 - 2009	
Maintenance, services , tune up, engine overhaul	Mechanic Assistance	

SKILLS & ATTRIBUTES

Programming

Java	Hibernate, Java Android	• • • • •
PHP	Native, Laravel, Yii, Code Igniter	• • • • •
ASP	Native ASP.net	• • • • •
Javascript	JQuery, NodeJS, AngularJS	• • • • •
Actionscript 3	AIR Native, Starling, Feathers	• • • • •
Front-end Web	Bootstrap, Foundation, LESS	• • • • •
Database	MySQL, MSSQL, PosgreSQL, MongoDB	• • • • •
Others		
Accounting	Book keeping, tax, financial	• • • • •
Management	Trello, milestone, scheduling, budgeting	• • • • •
English	Writting, speaking, listening	• • • • •
Networking	Server, LAN, Mikrotik, Routing	• • • • •
Operating System	Windows, Linux, Mac	• • • • •
Office Software	Word, Excel, Power Point	• • • • •

Design & Animation		
Hand Drawing	Illustration, perspective, character	\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet
Adobe Photoshop	Image Manipulation, Retouching	• • • • •
Adobe Flash	Animation, presentation	• • • • •
Adobe Illustrator	Icon & character design, prototyping	• • • • •
Adobe After Effect	Basic compositing, product showcase	• • • • •

PORTFOLIO

Currently I am working on a project: Orion Daily Life Saver and some entertainment games. I have done 10 more another projects like website, desktop app, mobile apps, and games, I hope nothing proud and over confident when i show you. This is just my effort to live and keep my belly full. So this is my notice to always low profile and keep learn.

